It's a pony kind of Christmas
小马们过的圣诞节
In every color shade
到处色彩缤纷
All around the world of Equestria
今天的小马国举国都在
It's Christmastime here today
迎接圣诞节来临
It's a pony kind of Christmas
小马们过的圣诞节
Its light never fades
其光芒不灭
All around the world of Equestria
今天的小马国举国欢庆
Christmas is here to stay
圣诞节已到来
Christmas is a time of joy
圣诞节欢乐无比
When the light of friendship burns bright
因友谊之光闪烁着
Takin' time for family
陪伴家人齐过节
To recall the past and do what's right
回忆过去并以此为鉴
And outside gentle snow is falling
看见门外正雪花飘飘
Forest creatures keeping warm below
林中生物在地下取暖
And all throughout Equestria
踏遍了小马国全境
We feel the light of friendship only grow
感受到友谊之光渐明亮
It's a pony kind of Christmas
小马们过的圣诞节
Its light never fades
其光芒不灭
All around the world of Equestria
今天的小马国举国欢庆
Christmas is here to stay
圣诞节已到来
Dashing through the snow
冲出大风雪
In a one-horse open sleigh
身后雪橇响叮当
Over the fields we go
我们飞奔过田野
Laughing all the way
欢笑又歌唱
Decorate with boughs of holly
用冬青的树枝装扮
Fill the halls with wonder
大厅满是惊喜
Wrap the presents, silver paper
用镀银纸来包礼物
Trim the tree and place them under
整理后并放在树下
Time for counting down the days to Christmas
是时候该倒数圣诞节了
Every day that passes is a party we can throw
每过的一天都值得开派对庆祝
Time for counting down the days to Christmas
是时候该倒数圣诞节了
And everyday our friendship grows
我们加深彼此友谊
It's a pony kind of Christmas
小马们过的圣诞节
In every color shade
到处色彩缤纷
All around the world of Equestria
小马国举国都在欢庆着
It's Christmastime here today
今天就是圣诞节
It's a pony kind of Christmas
小马们过的圣诞节
Its light never fades
其光芒不灭
All around the world of Equestria
今天的小马国举国欢庆
Christmas is here
圣诞节已
To stay
到来
翻译
蛟龙
校对
森林金雨
润色
蛟龙  森林金雨
时间轴
BronyDee
制作
习成 PBU 工作组
感谢观看